blinds.com 2012-10-29

# 

| **1.  How do I contact you?** | Back to Top  
---|---  
**Answer:**  
Call, email, mail, or fax us any questions. Our professional staff is eager to help you. All contact information is provided on the right side of every page of our site, including this one.  

**2.  Do you charge for shipping?** |    
**Answer:**  
If your products are all under 90" there is no charge for shipping anywhere in the Continental United States. For products wider than 94", shipping is $70.  

**3.  Do you ship catalogs or brochures?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
No, sorry. We try our best to make all of the information for our products available on our Web site including but not limited to measuring instructions, installation instructions, color charts and care & warranty information.  

**4.  Can I return the blinds I purchased?** |    
**Answer:**  
Since all products are custom, made-to-order for each customer they cannot be returned except for warranty repairs. Orders cannot be cancelled or modified once production has begun. When you follow our instructions we guarantee your blinds will fit perfectly. We understand that mistakes may occur and if we make a mistake on your order we will either repair or remake it at no charge to you. If you make a mistake in measuring or ordering please contact us. Depending on the type of error, you may return the product to the factory for alteration or we will have it remade at a discount.  

**5.  What methods of payment do you accept?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
We accept MasterCard, Visa, Discover, American Express, and personal or company checks.  

**6.  How long will it take to receive my order?** |    
**Answer:**  
Most orders are shipped as soon as they are completed. These times vary from product to product. If you ordered more than one brand they may arrive on different days depending on the manufacturers' production time and distance from your home or business.  

**7.  Do you charge sales tax?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
No, except in Texas at 8.25%.  

**8.  Can I change or cancel my order?** |    
**Answer:**  
Changes or cancellations can only be made during the first 12 hours and as long as your order has not gone into production. There is a 10% cancellation fee on orders that can be stopped. In most cases, no changes or cancellations can be made on one-day products.  

**9.  Do you ship outside of the continental U.S.?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
Please call for availability and rates. [Click here](http://www.blinds.com/control/infopage?page=freight_forwarders.html) for freight forwarding information and contacts.  

**10.  When do you charge my credit card?** |    
**Answer:**  
Since all of our products are custom made the credit card is charged before the order is placed into production. This usually happens within 24 hours of placing your order.  

**11.  How secure is my credit card online?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
When you place orders all of your information is processed through our secure server. We utilize industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology that encrypts all your information before it is sent to us. So it is very safe.  

**12.  Will I receive an order confirmation?** |    
**Answer:**  
Yes, you will receive an email confirmation of your order at the email address you provide. Please make sure that you thoroughly look over your order for accuracy. Remember, orders cannot be cancelled or returned for any reason once production has begun.  

**13.  Do you share any of my personal information?** | Back to Top  
  
**Answer:**  
We have never and will never share your personal information with anyone without your permission. We respect your privacy. All personal information you provide to us WILL remain absolutely confidential and be used solely to communicate better with you. Ways that we use information you provide us:

We use trusted third-party service providers to perform certain services on our behalf, including: shipping, payment processing, data storage/management, webhosting, web analytics, fulfillment, assembly, mailing, emailing, etc. These service providers only receive personal information if such information is needed to perform their function(s), and they are not authorized to use any personal information for any other purpose(s) other than the purpose(s) set forth by us. We use trusted third-party analytics and advertising companies to collect information about your visit. These companies may use information (but NOT your name, address, email address, telephone number or payment info!) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

We may, and you authorize us to use and disclose any information, including personal information: (1) we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; (2) in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any personal or as otherwise required by law; (3) to other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction; and (4) to enforce any agreement we have with you.

In some instances, we collect data through cookies, web logs, web beacons (also known as pixel gifs or action tags) and other monitoring technologies to enhance your browsing and shopping experience on our website. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive to collect information about your activities on our website. Web beacons are small strings of code placed on a web page or within an email for the purpose of transferring information. 

We use cookies and web beacons to deliver our web content, improve and measure the usability, track visits from our affiliates and partners, performance and effectiveness of our Website, improve and measure the effectiveness of our marketing programs, learn how customers use our website, estimate our audience size, deliver co-branded services, and to customize your shopping experience. Examples of the type of information that we collect through these collection devices, includes: total visitors to the website, pages viewed, unique visitors, time spent on our Website and on certain web pages, etc. You are always free to decline cookies if your browser permits; although, by declining the use of cookies you may not be able to use certain features on the Website.

We are committed to the protection of the personally identifiable information that you share with us. We utilize a combination of physical and electronic security technologies, procedures, and organizational measures to help protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When we transfer sensitive personal information (for example, credit card information) over the Internet, we protect it using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. While we strive to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and, accordingly, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us. 

If you are a California resident and would like a copy of our notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for their direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of the third parties and affiliates that received your information in the past year, please submit a written request to the following address: Global Custom Commerce at 10555 Richmond Ave Ste 200, Houston TX 77042; attn: California Privacy. Please allow up to 30 days for us to process your request. We are able to respond to one such a request per year.  

**14.  What if I don't see the product I wanted?** |    
**Answer:**  
We update our Website constantly. If there is a particular product you want but can't find it on our site then please call or email us at the number on the right side of this page.  

**15.  How can I find out what the product terms mean?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
We incorporate a comprehensive dictionary into the site that highlights terms that have fuller explanations. Just click on the blue underlined links and a small window will pop up with a brief explanation.  

**16.  Who is responsible for proper measurements?** |    
**Answer:**  
Please take extra time to measure ALL of your windows accurately. Since all of our products are custom made and are not returnable except for warranty repair, it is up to you to provide us with accurate sizes. You can find specific measuring instructions on each product page. Just look for the link titled "How To Measure" next to the product image. Measure EVERY window, and measure them twice to be sure. Sometimes two or three windows in the same room can look identical but could actually be off by as much as 3/4". General measuring instructions are found here.   

**17.  What if I measure something incorrectly?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
On most blinds we sell, we now offer the exclusive SureFit Guarantee for additional peace of mind. On others, we will do whatever we can to assist you with improperly measured blinds. Sometimes, if the measurement is only slightly off it can be resized at a nominal fee (sometimes free, except for shipping)- this depends entirely on how far off and what type of blind or shade it is.   

**18.  What if my blinds are damaged during shipping?** |    
**Answer:**  
We'll take care of any damage incurred during shipping.

IMPORTANT: Inspect your merchandise as soon as you receive it and notify us immediately if the merchandise has been damaged in shipment. Also, please check to make sure that the products you ordered were made exactly as you specified when you ordered them. If you notify us within 7 days of the date that the merchandise is delivered to you that the merchandise has been damaged in shipment or was made incorrectly, we will have the damaged merchandise either repaired or replaced at no cost to you. If you do not notify us that the merchandise has been damaged in shipment during this 7 day period, repairs or replacements cannot be made at no cost. All damaged shipments must be signed for as damaged.  

**19.  Which name brands do you carry?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
Levolor, Graber, , Prestige, Cartwright, Bali, Phifer, and many more.  

**20.  Which brand or type would be best for me?** |    
**Answer:**  
This depends on a number of factors. For more helpful advice click here or call us.  

**21.  Is there a shipping charge for oversized blinds?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
Please view our shipping policies here.  

**22.  Are these first quality? Do you sell seconds?** |    
**Answer:**  
We only sell first quality products; never seconds. They are made at the major name brand factories and shipped directly to you.  

**23.  Difference between inside & outside mount?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
An inside mount is when the blind, shade, or shutter fits inside of the window opening. Mounting as an inside mount generally has a cleaner, neater look. An outside mount can be used if there isn't enough depth to mount the product inside the opening. Sliding glass doors and wood cased shallow windows are popular outside mount choices.  

**24.  Will I be able to install these blinds myself?** |    
**Answer:**  
Absolutely. All of the products we sell are easy to install. With the information installation instructions found on our Web site and included along with your order, with a few simple hand tools you should easily be able to install all of the products we carry.  

**25.  What if I can't? Can you recommend someone?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
If you have a problem installing any of your products give our customer service department a call at the phone number on the right side of this page for guidance. If you don't feel comfortable installing them yourself, then ask our customer service department if they can recommend a third party installation firm to handle it for you.  

**26.  Do you supply all the necessary hardware?** |    
**Answer:**  
All of the necessary hardware including installation brackets are included with your blinds. Sometimes spacer blocks or shims may be needed and would need to be found at your local hardware store.  

**27.  Do you supply install screws and fasteners?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
Yes. However, there are many different types of mounting surfaces into which your products could be attached, such as concrete, wood, drywall, plaster, steel, etc. It's not feasible for manufacturers to include screws/fasteners that will work for all applications, but the ones included should work fine.  

**28.  Are the installation instructions included?** |    
**Answer:**  
The products come with the installation instructions in the box. If you can't find the instructions in the box, look on our Web site for your product and you'll find them there. Or, call our customer service department at the phone number on the right side of this page.  

**29.  How do I contact customer service?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
All contact information is shown on the right side of all the pages of our site (including this page).  

**30.  What type of product warranty do you have?** |    
**Answer:**  
Specific warranty information is shown on each product page. Just look for the link to the right of the main product image near the top of the page.

Manufacturers usually offer Limited Lifetime Warranties.  

**31.  How do I check order status?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
Call the number on this and every page and we'll check.  

**32.  How do I clean and care for my blinds?** |    
**Answer:**  
Specific care and warranty information is shown on each product page. Just look for the link to the right of the main product image near the top of the page.  

**33.  What if one of my blinds breaks?** | Back to Top  
**Answer:**  
We're here to help. Just call the number on this page and ask for the Customer Service Department. One of our experienced associates will help you.
